<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Tianqi</title>
    <link>https://Timothy802.github.io/website/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Tianqi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>tianqi93@connect.hku.hk (Tianqi)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>tianqi93@connect.hku.hk (Tianqi)</webMaster><atom:link href="https://Timothy802.github.io/website/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://Timothy802.github.io/website/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>tianqi93@connect.hku.hk (Tianqi)</author>
      <guid>https://Timothy802.github.io/website/page/about/</guid>
      <description>I am currently a first-year PhD student in the Department of Speech and Hearing Science at The University of Hong Kong. I am working on the psychology of language under the supervision of Dr. Manwa Lawrence Ng and Dr. Xu Xu. In particular, I am using computational models, including machine learning and deep learning, to understand the processing of lexical and semantic representation in both comprehension and production. Prior to my study in HKU, I received graduate training in Shanghai Jiao Tong University, and worked as a research assistant in Shenzhen Institutes of Advanced Technology, Chinese Academy of Sciences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://Timothy802.github.io/website/page/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>tianqi93@connect.hku.hk (Tianqi)</author>
      <guid>https://Timothy802.github.io/website/page/publications/</guid>
      <description>Conference Paper Wang, T., Lian, C., Pan, J., Yan, Q., Zhu, F., Ng, M., Wang, L., &amp;amp; Yan, N. (2019). Towards the speech features of mild cognitive impairment: Universal evidence from structured and unstructured connected speech of Chinese. Interspeech 2019 (EI) [PDF]
Wang, T., Yan, Q., Pan, J., Zhu, F., Su, R., Guo, Y., Wang, L., &amp;amp; Yan, N. (2019). Towards the speech features of early-stage dementia: Design and application of the Mandarin elderly cognitive speech database.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
